VICTOR AYOMIPO

WEB DEVELOPER. TECHNICAL WRITER

□ vayospot@gmail.com

234-703-931-5618

https://github.com/Vayyo

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- · Sass, TailwindCSS
- NodeJS
- HTML & CSS
- Technical Writing
- Content Writing
- Marketing
- Al Proficiency

I'm a practical front-end developer, proud of everything I work on. I take pride in building interesting web apps, debugging, and simplifying complex ideas. Skilled in JavaScript and the likes of React, Tailwind, etc. Even grandmas would be impressed by the results I produce. Let's build the ultimate user experience through your platform.

In my spare time, I tinker with algorithms and AI to build my own games. Because what's more fun than making a computer do what you want it to do?

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER (FRONTEND)

Aug 2021 - Present

Upwork

- Fashioned a website so responsive, it could adapt to screens of all sizes, from a smartwatch to an IMAX screen,
- Developed web games using algorithms like DFS that are nearly undefeatable by users
- Learnt the art of debugging websites through a simple but effective means called "Dynamic Error Tracing"
- Collaborated closely with designers and backend experts, thus acquiring invaluable knowledge.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Jan 2021 - May 2021

Al's Pet

- Crafted an impressive website from scratch, giving a solid boost of 15% to the business's sales!
- Developed prototypes and mockups for 5 new features, making the UI design shine like never before!
- Sprinkled some magic on the website, thus reducing page load times by a whopping 40% using a clever media conversion trick!

TECHNICAL WRITER

Mar 2023 - Present

Semaphore

- Authored engaging articles about AI tools that make developers' lives easier, that they could immediately put into action.
- Developed content focusing on effective app marketing strategies for developers, helping them reach wider audiences and boost their app's success.
- Worked magic with SEO tactics to optimize articles for increased visibility and search engine rankings.

EDUCATION

BIOCHEMISTRY
Olabisi Onabanjo University

Oct 2017 - Jan 2021

STRENGTH

- Eager to learn from the best.
- Time management, never waste a minute.
- Problem solver: cracks codes effortlessly.
- Reliable teammate, dependable through thick-and-thin.